Good afternoon ladies and gentlemen. No, sorry. Hi and welcome to this video again.
In this video I'm going to talk about these two leggings from Slinky Styles.
And you may have seen them on my Instagram account pictures because I wear them a lot, especially these ones.
And so I thought I'm going to tell you my opinion about them.
So starting with this pair of leggings, it's called Cheeky Wedge and there's another weird
name with a lot of numbers and letters. I'll put them in the description box down below
so you can find them more easily on the wedgeshop and on their webshop, sorry.
The material is overall kind of stretchy and the waistband itself is pretty firm,
like there is a front contouring which you can see on the website it has
different levels and I prefer like front contouring zero or whatever so the same
goes for the back contouring the booty contouring this one has a really special
seam here which is going to push up the bum a bit and I think it really makes a
difference if this weird ruffled seam is there or not and you'll see why. So
that's the easy part because it's really smooth and stretchy fabric it's super
comfortable to wear. When it comes to the waistband I really have to pull the
leggings up with force so it'll fit in all the right places. According to the
product information it is necessary and not tearing the leggings apart at all
and when I first put them on I was really afraid to rip them apart somehow
but it didn't happen and now they really cling to my figure and the firm waistband
makes a really fat stomach. Also this is a really smooth transition from leggings
to body and even though I don't work out it shapes my booty a great deal or at
least that's what I like to think.
The second pair of leggings I want to show you is this one called Rubber Touch.
Again I'll link you the name in the description box.
This one is slightly different from the one I showed you first because obviously it's a different
kind of material. It's matte, it's still a bit stretchy but not as stretchy as the one before.
It's a different cut here because of this thingy called Rollwiese in German.
I have no idea what's German-English.
Which means there's a seam at the back of the leg but not at the inside of the leg.
I hope you get what I mean.
The wristband has a great fit again.
It's a bit too loose around the knees for me though but that's
problem I have with most leggings. And there you can see the Rollwiese. It makes a nice
booty shape and runs down the length of the leg. As I mentioned there is no seam
at the sides of the legs which makes the leggings really comfortable again and
adds to the smooth look.
Hello!
If you want to know more about the company I can tell you a few facts I put together.
And goodbye cat.
This is not some kind of mass production in Asia but it's a small company located in the
south of Germany.
They fit really really good.
That's why I really like to wear them.
And there is a standard product line where you can buy the off the shelf sizes and they
They also have a made to measure or rather customizable solution.
They are not only producing leggings but if you check out their website you may find skirts
as well for example.
I hope I could provide you with some information about these slinky styles leggings.
Hit the subscribe button if you did not already and have a nice day.
Bye.
Thank you.